#### Contact

sorayah.bourenane@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sorayahb (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing

Healthcare

Hospitals

### Languages

English

French

### Certifications

Certified Emergency Nurse (CEN)
Clinical Nurse Leader (CNL)

# Sorayah Bourenane, MSN, RN, CEN, CNL

Certified Emergency Nurse (CEN) | Clinical Nurse Leader (CNL) | Emergency Center & Clinical Decision Unit

Houston, Texas

## Summary

Certified Clinical Nurse Leader focused on patient satisfaction and quality of care with a demonstrated history of working in the entertainment, hospital & health care industries. Skilled in quality improvement, data analysis, emergency nursing, oncologic emergencies, Percussion / Music Education and Event Management. Strong program and project management rapport with interdisciplinary focus, skilled communicator and process change expert.

# Experience

MD Anderson Cancer Center 5 years 10 months

Clinical Nurse Leader June 2019 - Present (1 year)

Houston, Texas

Clinical Nurse Leader June 2019 - Present (1 year)

Houston, Texas Area

**Emergency Center & Clinical Decision Unit** 

Registered Nurse

August 2014 - Present (5 years 10 months)

Houston, Texas

**Emergency RN** 

Clinical Resource Nurse June 2016 - June 2019 (3 years 1 month)

Houston, Texas

**Drumline Instructor** 

Drumline Instructor
June 2012 - Present (8 years)

Texas

Drumline Technician; Bass Drum Instruction

John Horn HS - Mesquite, TX\*
Frisco Centennial HS - Frisco, TX\*
Argyle HS - Argyle, TX\*
Foster HS - Richmond, TX\*
Rancho Cucamonga HS - RC, CA
Clinton High School - Clinton, TN

Eye-5 Model Staffing Agency Staff Manager June 2008 - August 2015 (7 years 3 months) USA

Previous Events: Coachella, SXSW, Quakecon, Comicon, CES, E3, Lady Gaga, USA Network, BravoTV, La Prairie Skin Care, Google, Macallan/ Highland Park/Famous Grouse, Brides Magazine (...)

MD Anderson Cancer Center Professional Student Nurse Extern May 2013 - May 2014 (1 year 1 month) Houston, TX

Texas Woman's University
Student Nurse
August 2012 - May 2014 (1 year 10 months)

Mesa Lounge
2 years 8 months

Reservations Manager
July 2011 - January 2014 (2 years 7 months)

Special Events Manager
June 2011 - July 2012 (1 year 2 months)

## Education

Texas Woman's University

Master of Science (M.S.), Clinical Nurse Leader · (2016 - 2019)

Texas Woman's University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012 - 2014)

Mt. San Antonio College

Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2009 - 2012)

University of Tennessee

N/a, Communications and Public Relations · (2007 - 2008)